smallseotoolz.com 2016-06-16

# Privacy Policy | Small SEO Tools

#### Privacy Policy

__**06/01/2016 12:00 AM**

* * *

## ****SmallSeoToolz.com**  Customer  **Privacy****

### ****Privacy**  Policy**

### We encourage our visitors to read out our Policy carefully. If you have any questions or suggestion about this Policy, use of your Personal Info, or your dealings with this website, please feel free to contact us. We may update this Policy at any without any notice in our use of your Personal Information and/or applicable law. Any modification made to this  **Privacy**  Policy will be reflected in an updated policy (denoted by an updated date above) posted on our website at  **SmallSeoToolz.com**.

### **Collection of Your Personal Information**

The Customers who use the products or services available from our website (collectively, the “Services”) do so freely. In order to use our free Services, a customer is optionally required to create an account by registering and providing us the basic contact, billing and website information, including, but not limited to, such customer’s name, email address and website URL. By providing us with Personal Information, customers are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of such Personal Information in agreement with the terms and conditions set forth in this Policy.

### **How We Use Personal Information**

Any Personal Information about collected by us is strictly used for only billing purpose, contacting our customers, evaluating a prospective customer’s website content, and for such other purpose as are described in this Policy.  **SmallSeoToolz.com**  does not share any customer Personal Information with any third party other than those business partners who are directly involved in managing our day to day business operations, such as, without drawback, our billing and payment processes. We reserve the right to release your Personal Information without notice or permission as it deems necessary (a) to conform to applicable law; (b) when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and property; (c) to protect the safety of our users, us, or other third parties; (d) to comply with any judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us; and/or (e) pursuant to an acquisition, merger, sale of assets or other business transfer.

### **Log Files**

By accessing our website, our servers automatically trace information that your web browser sends when you browse a website. These logs may contain information such as IP address, web browser version, domain name, language, date and time, the referring website and information in your cookie files.

### **Third Party Advertisements**

The advertisements appear on our website from time to time are provided by a variety of our third party partners. We only share website usage information about our users with trustworthy third party advertisers for the only purpose of better targeting our website banner advertisements.

### **Website Cookies**

To permit our customers the convenience of not having to memorize theirs login information when accessing our website, **SmallSeoToolz.com**  may place a temporary or constant “cookie” on your computer’s hard drive. These cookies are simple, harmless text files that remember the internet browser you used to access the internet. On the other hand, if you do no want to receive cookies, you may adjust the settings in your internet browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. We do not save or store any Personal Information via cookies.

### **General Internet User   **Privacy****

In order to collect and aggregate statistical data for our customers, we may from time to time place persistent or temporary cookies on a visitor’s hard drive when visiting a customer’s website. These cookies are not capable of tracking, retaining, or storing any own Information, and they are used for no other cause than to gather the same common internet information that is available to all internet service providers, search engines, and websites. Examples of this information include, without limitation, a visitor’s general location based on IP address, information from the visitor’s browser such as browser type, operating system, keywords used while searching, and websites visited, monitor resolution settings. We may from time to time also authorize and help the use of cookies from trusted third party business partners to gather and aggregate additional, anonymous, and non-Personal Information data from general internet visitors for the purpose of providing our customers with additional information about their viewing viewers. We do not gather, retain or store any data from these third-party partners. We have also chosen to partner only with businesses that have shown a strong assurance to online  **privacy**  and have represented and warranted to Us that any and all data collected on our behalf is non-Personal Information. We do not excuse, support, or contribute in any activities that could potentially gather, retrieve or store any Personal Information about or from internet users.

### **Links to Other Websites**

Our website contains links to other sites that are not owned by us. Please be aware that we are not answerable for the  **privacy**  practices of such third party websites and this Policy does not govern such other websites or your use of them. This Policy applies only to information collected by our website. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the  **privacy**  policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

1\. For an inclusive list of definitions and what constitutes “personally identifiable information” please visit http://www.w3.org/TR/1998/WD-P3P10-harmonization-19980330

2\. For additional information Regarding Cookies please see –  **http://www.bbbonline.org/UnderstandingPrivacy/toolbox/cookies.asp**

Additional Information Regarding Online  **Privacy**  Can Be Found At:

**http://www.bbbonline.org**

**http://www.privacyalliance.org**

**http://www.truste.org**

### **Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, using cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network  **privacy**  policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to offer advertisements about goods and services likely to be of bigger importance to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit

**http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.**
